MAKSYM SHTARKBERG



♠ Afula **** 0538926485 **** starkberg@icloud.com

GitHub Linked In

https://github.com/maksymshtarkberg

https://www.linkedin.com/in/maksym-shtarkberg/

SUMMARY

Frontend Developer with 2 years of commercial experience. Proven skills in building complex applications, modularization and dynamic forms, with a specialization in React. Looking for interesting projects and new people to share experience and enhance skills.

SKILLS

JavaScript | TypeScript | React | Redux | Next | Node.js(Express, Apollo) | REST API | GraphQL | Prisma | Python(Telethon) | GIT

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer 2023 - current

JavaScript | TypeScript | React | Redux | Next | REST API

Noviopus, Rishon LeZion

Worked remotely with a great Israeli Job-search start-up project.

- Migrate React app to Next.js 14 for SSR and SSG rendering.
- Implement i18next to Next.js with dynamic translation route.
- Project architecture strategy and optimization of SEO.

Web Developer 2022 - 2023

JavaScript | TypeScript | React | Next | Node.js(Apollo) | REST API | GraphQL | Prisma

Mono Software, Osijek

Worked remotely with a great software company.

- Created accessible, responsive and functional user interfaces to allow visitors on any device.
- Developed back-end in Node.js with accordance to industry and company standards.
- Learned multiple threading, concurrency, technologies and their impact on application concurrency back-end business logic and API.

Frontend Web Developer

2021 - 2022

$JavaScript \mid TypeScript \mid React \mid Redux \mid Node.js(Express) \mid REST \; API$

MeGaDev Ilc, Kharkiv

Worked with a great outsourcing start-up team.

- Developed a responsive and user-friendly Single Page Application (SPA).
- Optimized performance of React rendering, API handlers.
- Performed unit/integration testing.

EDUCATION

Master of Financial security of Banks 2015 - 2017

Kharkiv Educational and Scientific Institute of SHEI "Banking University"

Bachelor of Banking 2010 - 2015

Kharkiv Educational and Scientific Institute of SHEI "Banking University"

LANGUAGES

English B2 | Hebrew A2 | Russian Native | Ukrainian Native